<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>STAT 7200 - Winter 2020</title>
    <link>https://turgeonmaxime.github.io/w20-stat7200/</link>
    <description>Recent content on STAT 7200 - Winter 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://turgeonmaxime.github.io/w20-stat7200/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Problems</title>
      <link>https://turgeonmaxime.github.io/w20-stat7200/practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://turgeonmaxime.github.io/w20-stat7200/practice/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of practice problems.
 Problem set 1 Problem set 2 Problem set 3 Problem set 4  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://turgeonmaxime.github.io/w20-stat7200/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://turgeonmaxime.github.io/w20-stat7200/slides/</guid>
      <description>Slides  Course Overview Review of Linear Algebra  R code   Multivariate Distibutions  R code   Multivariate Normal Distribution  R code   Elliptical Distributions  R code Hofert, M. (2013). On sampling from the multivariate t distribution. The R Journal.   Wishart Distribution  R code Blog post on different decompositions for random matrices   Test for multivariate means  R code   Test for covariance matrices  R code R code for downloading Winnipeg weather data    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supplementary Material</title>
      <link>https://turgeonmaxime.github.io/w20-stat7200/suppl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://turgeonmaxime.github.io/w20-stat7200/suppl/</guid>
      <description>Supplementary Material On this page, I will post additional resources and supplementary material for the course.
Resources for R In this course, we will use R as the main computational tool. Below are some resources:
 R for Data Science by Grolemund and Wickham. Hands-On Programming with R by Grolemund. Jenny Bryan&#39;s course on Data wrangling, exploration, and analysis with R  In particular, I recommend the notes on The Many Flavours of R objects   Mine Cetinkaya&#39;s curated list of resources for R If you&#39;re looking for a deep understanding of R, I recommend Hadley Wickham&#39;s book Advanced R RStudio has several great cheatsheets on their website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>